

CONTACT

- **&** 8667092386
- itsmedevadharshini@gmail.com
- Madurai, Tamilnadu, India.
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/de vadharshini-karthikeyan-051b401b1/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS, SAAS
- Bootstrap
- Angular 8 to Angular 15
- Javascript, Typescript
- Figma
- CMS

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Responsive Web Design
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Continuous learning
- Effective Communication
- Flexibility & Adaptability

LANGUAGES

- English
- Tamil
- Telugu

DEVADHARSHINI

ANGULAR UI DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Professional Angular UI Developer with over 3 years of experience, specializing in website development and dedicated to enhancing user experience. I've honed my skills in Angular, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, and Figma. Successfully designed the company website, resulting in a 70% increase in user interaction.

WORK EXPERIENCE

NB Media Tech Pvt Ltd.,

Dec 2023 - Present

UI/UX DEVELOPER

- Design and Develop user interfaces for Web Development by using Angular, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript to develop user interface components and features.
- To ensure that the designs can automatically adapt to different screen sizes and devices.

Refresh Marketing

Jun 2023 - Nov 2023

Mid Level Web Developer

- Create and develop the website using custom CMS for the client, Converting Figma designs into HTML, Angular, and CSS, with Bootstrap as the framework.
- Design and implement UI components and features that automatically adapt to various screen sizes and devices.

Osiz Technologies Pvt Ltd

May 2022 - May 2023

Junior Designer

- Design and Develop user interfaces for website using Angular, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and JavaScript.
- Create a template for the client in Figma, incorporating design elements related to NFT, DeFi, and Education.

Nexconz Solutions

Jun 2021 - Feb 2022

Junior Developer - Trainee

- Develop and test code for the website, address and fix bugs, and maintain code. Handle minor bug fixes as needed.
- Worked on a client project by gathering requirements and developing a website using HTML, CSS, and Angular

EDUCATION

Kalasalingam Institute of Technology

2017 - 2021

Bachelor of Engineering - Computer Science

Coursework: Web development, Software engineering, Operating Systems, Computer Graphics, Computer Architecture, Computer Programming.

CGPA: 8.14 First Class with Distinction